<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Crossing Lines</title><link href="http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/feeds/all-en.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/</id><updated>2013-04-09T12:05:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>I'm Sad This Morning</title><link href="http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/sad-morning.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-04-09T12:05:00+02:00</updated><author><name>someone you know</name></author><id>tag:crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines,2013-04-09:sad-morning.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This morning while working I suddenly became desperately, desperately sad.  I put my face in my hands and just curled up in a ball for several minutes.  Lately, whenever I see a girl, I'm filled with this immense sense of longing and deep, pit-of-the-stomach sadness.  Maybe I'm crazy, but I feel different flavors of sadness in different parts of the body.  For example, I feel the embarrassed, oops-I-made-a-mess sadness in the back of my throat.  The sadness I feel when I'm watching a sad movie is somewhere in the back of my mouth.  This sadness feels like being punched in the stomach.  It's a really hard emotion to describe; it's a sadness for something I'll never be, a longing that knows it will never be fulfilled, a weariness of being myself and not what I want to be.  I'm sure other people have deep-seeded longings that can never be fulfilled as well, but most of those things could at least in theory be fulfilled, right?  Someone might have a deep desire to date a particular movie star.  This could at least in theory happen, so it's not quite the same thing.  I guess someone could want to be taller than they are, and being a grown adult know that they will never grow another six inches, but how much of your identity is wrapped up in how tall you are?  Conversely, how much of your identity is wrapped up in your gender?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being a biologically male heterosexual further complicates things.  When I see a pretty girl, I have a very confusing mix of at least three emotions, and it's very hard to tell where one ends and the other begins.  First, I often see girls as pretty—that is, aesthetically pleasing, beautiful from an artists point of view.  The second emotional reaction is physical attraction or sexual desire.  I think a lot of artistically minded men have a confusing experience conflating these first two.  But the third emotion makes things unbearably complicated, confusing, and terrifyingly, desperately, overwhelmingly saddening.  The third reaction is a deep-seeded desire to &lt;em&gt;be&lt;/em&gt; that person I'm looking at.  This third reaction often happens with unattractive girls too:  I'll look at a girl who has clearly let herself go and think, &amp;quot;You've got everything I ever wanted, right there between your legs.  I'd give anything to be you, to have what you have, and you did &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; with it?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This morning what set me off was seeing a random girl in skinny jeans and these cute knee-high boots.  On a scale of one to ten, my emotional reactions of the three types were roughly a six for the first type, really only a two or three for the second type (I had sex with my wife just last night, and when I've been having a lot of sex this one really isn't a problem), and a ten for the third type.  Hence the curling up in a ball and wanting to hide from the world.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="C-word free"></category><category term="emotions"></category></entry><entry><title>And so it begins</title><link href="http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/and-so-it-begins.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-03-18T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>someone you know</name></author><id>tag:crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines,2013-03-18:and-so-it-begins.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;So I've been working on getting this site set up for almost a week now, and I feel like I should have something important and grandiose to say in my first post, but I don't.  Enjoy the blog, and check out the about page to figure out what's going on here.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="C-word free"></category></entry></feed>