<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Crossing Lines</title><link href="http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/feeds/posts.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/</id><updated>2013-04-09T13:30:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>The Change Question</title><link href="http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/the-change-question.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-04-09T13:30:00+02:00</updated><author><name>someone you know</name></author><id>tag:crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines,2013-04-09:the-change-question.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Anyone who is transgender or transsexual and has been reading my blog is probably screaming at me to go ahead and change already.  In short:  it's not that simple, and I'm pretty sure I don't want to anyway.  Here's the long version.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As long as I can remember (I think at least, experience always colors memory), I have wished that I was born a girl.  I didn't even know that a person could become another sex until I was in my late teens.  As a child, the distinction between gender and sex were never pointed out to me, so I just assumed that I was a boy who just happened to feel like it sucks to be a boy.  I never considered the idea that my psychological gender and my biological sex could be mismatched until I learned that such things existed in college.  I often wonder how my life would be different if my parents had recognized such things and been much more open to me expressing my feelings about this sort of thing.  But they weren't, and I can't go back and change that no matter how much I want to, just like I can't go back and be born a girl even though I desperately want to.  The point is that I am what I am now, and the question is what to do &lt;em&gt;now&lt;/em&gt;, not what &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; I have done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I'm in my twenties.  I'm most definitely attracted to women and not men.  Again, I have no idea how things would be different if I had been raised as a girl; I think if I had gone through puberty as a girl, I would be either attracted to men or asexual.  But again, that's not what happened, and I am what I am now.  Now I get weirded out by the concept that the desire to dress up like a girl should be correlated with the desire to stick a penis in your mouth.  I definitely like wearing women's clothing, but having sex with a man is repulsive to me, and the societal association of this behavior with the wearing of feminine clothing often scares me away from expressing myself in this manner.  As a side note, I think if I had a vagina I would want to put a penis in it, but since I have a penis, I like putting my penis in my wife's vagina.  Yes, I said wife.  I'm married, which of course complicates things further.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm deeply in love with my wife, and I would never want to do anything to hurt her.  She knows about my gender issues (though probably not the full extent, though I've tried not to hide anything from her).  She is quite supportive to the extent that she can be, but she's also still getting used to the idea that I'm not always happy with being a male.  I was an athlete in college, and as such I have (or had, back when I worked out more) a relatively attractive male upper body.  I had pretty a pretty muscular chest and abs, and I still have the broad shoulders characteristic of athletes in my sport.  My wife is not the kind of girl to walk around swooning over muscular guys with their shirts off, but she definitely wasn't opposed to my build when I was training in college.  I think she's having a bit of trouble getting her mind around the idea that someone with such masculine features could have so much inward conflict about gender.  She definitely believes me and still loves me no matter what, but I think she's just confused.  I don't blame her, I'm confused too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This brings me to another reason why &amp;quot;changing&amp;quot; would be difficult, if not also undesirable:  I'm very much built like a man.  When I dress up in girls clothing, I usually only wear skirts and shoes or other things on my lower body.  Putting girl's tops or dresses on my manly shoulders still freaks me out.  Practically speaking, I doubt there probably isn't a surgery that could make me look like a normal girl, even if I wanted it.  I'm also tall, over six feet, so I would stand out in the crowd as a female even if the other things could be changed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than practical concerns, though, I don't know if I'd want to &amp;quot;change&amp;quot; even if I could.  Given some magic spell that would make me into a normal-looking female version of myself, with no social consequences or anything else, I would pretty much always go for that.  But the amount of depression I have from not being female comes and goes.  It's always there, dull in the back of my mind, but it's not always (or even usually) intense enough to have desires of doing anything drastic.  In the more realistic scenario that I had been offered the opportunity to transition as a child, I'm not sure if I would have or not.  The sadness is pretty bad at times, but there are still some difficult trade-offs, like losing the ability to reproduce.  If I could be a normal girl, I would love that.  But I can't, and I love the rest of my life that I would lose if that happened (even if it could).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thinking long and hard about it, I think what I really want now that I am the way that I am is for people to accept me as me.  I want to be able to wear skirts and cute heels in public, to paint my fingernails and toenails, to wear my hair in pigtails or double French braids.  I want to get my belly button pierced and shave my legs.  I want to wear skinny jeans tucked in to tall black boots with stiletto heels.  I want to get a distinctly feminine nose piercing and wear a tiny, sparkly, pink stud in it.  You can call me he or she or whatever, I don't really care.  I want to keep being married to my awesome wife and keep being the man she loves.  I want to keep having amazing married sex with my wife.  I want to keep working at my job that I love without anyone thinking differently about me, or at least without anyone thinking less of me.  I want to have children and be a good daddy to them.  I want to grow old with my wife and live a happy, full life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But that approach will never work.  It'll never happen that way.  Because if there's one thing that people accept and understand less than a transgendered person, it's someone who is between.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="sex"></category><category term="the future"></category></entry><entry><title>I'm Sad This Morning</title><link href="http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/sad-morning.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-04-09T12:05:00+02:00</updated><author><name>someone you know</name></author><id>tag:crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines,2013-04-09:sad-morning.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This morning while working I suddenly became desperately, desperately sad.  I put my face in my hands and just curled up in a ball for several minutes.  Lately, whenever I see a girl, I'm filled with this immense sense of longing and deep, pit-of-the-stomach sadness.  Maybe I'm crazy, but I feel different flavors of sadness in different parts of the body.  For example, I feel the embarrassed, oops-I-made-a-mess sadness in the back of my throat.  The sadness I feel when I'm watching a sad movie is somewhere in the back of my mouth.  This sadness feels like being punched in the stomach.  It's a really hard emotion to describe; it's a sadness for something I'll never be, a longing that knows it will never be fulfilled, a weariness of being myself and not what I want to be.  I'm sure other people have deep-seeded longings that can never be fulfilled as well, but most of those things could at least in theory be fulfilled, right?  Someone might have a deep desire to date a particular movie star.  This could at least in theory happen, so it's not quite the same thing.  I guess someone could want to be taller than they are, and being a grown adult know that they will never grow another six inches, but how much of your identity is wrapped up in how tall you are?  Conversely, how much of your identity is wrapped up in your gender?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being a biologically male heterosexual further complicates things.  When I see a pretty girl, I have a very confusing mix of at least three emotions, and it's very hard to tell where one ends and the other begins.  First, I often see girls as pretty—that is, aesthetically pleasing, beautiful from an artists point of view.  The second emotional reaction is physical attraction or sexual desire.  I think a lot of artistically minded men have a confusing experience conflating these first two.  But the third emotion makes things unbearably complicated, confusing, and terrifyingly, desperately, overwhelmingly saddening.  The third reaction is a deep-seeded desire to &lt;em&gt;be&lt;/em&gt; that person I'm looking at.  This third reaction often happens with unattractive girls too:  I'll look at a girl who has clearly let herself go and think, &amp;quot;You've got everything I ever wanted, right there between your legs.  I'd give anything to be you, to have what you have, and you did &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; with it?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This morning what set me off was seeing a random girl in skinny jeans and these cute knee-high boots.  On a scale of one to ten, my emotional reactions of the three types were roughly a six for the first type, really only a two or three for the second type (I had sex with my wife just last night, and when I've been having a lot of sex this one really isn't a problem), and a ten for the third type.  Hence the curling up in a ball and wanting to hide from the world.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="C-word free"></category><category term="emotions"></category></entry><entry><title>And so it begins</title><link href="http://crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines/and-so-it-begins.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-03-18T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>someone you know</name></author><id>tag:crossing-lines.github.com/crossing-lines,2013-03-18:and-so-it-begins.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;So I've been working on getting this site set up for almost a week now, and I feel like I should have something important and grandiose to say in my first post, but I don't.  Enjoy the blog, and check out the about page to figure out what's going on here.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><category term="C-word free"></category></entry></feed>